Do you want me to start by saying it's the final season
「ファイナル・シーズン」って 言い方で始めたほうがいいかな？
or, like, season ten?
それとも「シーズン10」？
We've been knocking on doors for ten seasons.
10シーズンにわたって、 僕たちは扉を叩き続けてきた。
Behind every door is a story.
扉の向こうには、それぞれの物語がある。
Oh my God!
なんてこと！
For our final season, we are in the eye of the storm.
ファイナル・シーズン、 僕たちは嵐の目の中にいる。
Welcome to Washington, DC.
ワシントンD.C.へようこそ。
We're here to give you a gorgeous makeover.
君をゴージャスに 変身させるために来たよ。
-Here we go! -They're so excited.
-いくよ！ -みんなすごく興奮してる。
-You're not, though. -No.
-でも、あなたは違うみたいね。 -ああ。
Every one of us knows somebody
愛や支え、コミュニティを必要としている
that needs love, support, community.
誰かを、誰もが知っているはずだ。
I feel like I've been broken.
心が折れてしまったみたい。
I want her to be happy.
彼女には幸せになってほしい。
Surviving is one thing, but living is another.
生き延びることと、人生を 謳歌することは別物だ。
To strengthen these sisters' bond,
姉妹の絆を深めるためには、
they need to learn to accept each other's differences.
お互いの違いを受け入れる ことを学ばなければならない。
She never turned her back on me.
彼女は決して僕を見捨てなかった。
But when you had to fight at home just to be yourself,
でも、ただ自分らしくいるために 家の中で戦わなければならなかったことが、
that was the hardest part growing up gay.
ゲイとして育つ中で一番辛いことだった。
When you're a teacher in a school,
学校の教師をしていると、
you feel like the world is right here in this building.
この建物の中に 世界があるように感じるんだ。
Despite a lot of the stuff that terrifies me in the world right now,
今、世界には恐ろしいことが たくさんあるけれど、
every personal human experience that I've had
僕が経験してきた人間としての 個人的な体験のひとつひとつが、
has deepened my faith that everything's gonna be okay.
すべては大丈夫だという 確信を深めてくれた。
You have an option to live the life that you wanna live.
あなたには、自分が望む 人生を生きる選択肢がある。
This is just the start of a whole new chapter for both of you.
これは二人にとって、まったく 新しい章の始まりに過ぎない。
I didn't think I needed this, but I needed this.
これが必要だなんて思わなかった けど、必要だった。
Anything can change if a person experiences real love.
本当の愛を知れば、 どんなことだって変えられる。
The fight that we started season one is still going strong,
シーズン1から始めた戦いは 今も力強く続いていて、
and even after we're gone, it will continue on.
僕たちがいなくなった後も、 それは続いていくだろう。
Will y'all marry me?
みんな、僕と結婚してくれる？
Yes, we will. We will.
もちろん。喜んで。